Dallas, 75228

Email: georgia.andree2@gmail.com

Cell: 214-500-0411

Summary

Accomplished Fortune 500 Structured Senior Sales and Marketing Professional, with over ten years of elaborate Corporate, SMB and Start-up knowledge and skills. Especially skilled in Technology Brokering – interdepartmental communications with IT, vendor selection, vendor negotiations, software implementation and employee training.

Highlights

Corporate website content alignment High Performance Sales record Marketing automation implementation Strategic account development Brand/Product development Complex Project management
Multi-media and interactive marketing
Social Media Presence & Accountability
Media Communications Relations
Global Account Management

Accomplishments

<u>Marketing & Media:</u> Successfully rejuvenated IT company's online presence, website, and collateral. 12 month cycle, website statistics increased: new visitors 400%, returning visitors 23%, reduced bounce rate by 27% and unique pageviews increased over 200%.

Sales: Achieved over 300% of \$20M quota 2008 and 2009, and 219% of 2007 quota. Awards: 2008 / 2009 -100% Club winner, 2007- received IBM GM Influencer Award.

<u>Start-up:</u> Created Startup sales and marketing program for StravinSOFT, Inc. – team had established \$190,000 pipeline in 2 months.

<u>Field & Direct Marketing:</u> Field marketing events generated approx. \$2.5M in revenue in one year, and approx. 50 open qualified leads, with approx. \$2.5M in expected revenue for 2003. Developed Nine (9) - tactic direct-mail campaigns, with first generating a 12% response rate and a 5% qualified lead rate.

Experience

Freelance Consultant & Student

September 2013 to current

KEDAR INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES (KEDARit)

Director, Business Development - BPM Sales, ITIL 2011 Foundations Certified **Media and Marketing Director**

February 2012 to September 2013

- Overhaul of company website to include uniform branding and SEO implementation. Web traffic increased 200%.
- Implemented automated marketing solution, including website and CRM integration.
- Ongoing email campaign design and implementation, including list selection, target market analysis, lead tracking, reporting, and sales support.
- Implemented company Social Media presence/campaign(s), including Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google+ utilizing tools such as Hoot suite, Tweet deck, Google analytics, Raven and Moz.
- Initiated further corporate branding presence/consistency by updating all marketing collateral (including web and hard copy versions).
- Conceptual development and implementation of various marketing projects, including Analyst comparisons, author and record company video, as well as automated product commercials.
- Events & Tradeshow participation, including development of 2013 event calendar and budgets, prep and attend shows (signage, collateral booth furniture, giveaways etc.)
- Partner program updates, including assist in revamp of affiliate program documentation, and development of joint campaigns email and/or webinars.
- Positioned company for purchase or investors through revamp of Investor package, and key introductions.

IBM

September 2006 to March 2010

Senior Client Representative

- Highly successful Territory management, Relationship management and Opportunity ownership.
- Driving double-digit revenue growth across the territories of small and medium businesses by seeking out high-value, high-growth opportunities in existing or new IBM IT or LOB customers.

- Knowledge of IBM's e-business strategy, products, offerings and solutions as well as being skilled in IBM's Signature Selling Method and consultative sales techniques.
- Worked closely with C-Level Executives to determine customer business by possessing a high level of customer and industry savvy with the ability to communicate clearly with all levels of contacts.
- Creative problem solving coupled with the establishment of a consultative partnership with the customer that rapidly turned needs and requirements into high-value opportunities.

ALASKA USA FEDERAL CREDIT UNION Technical Training Officer

September 2005 to September 2006

- Developed blended-learning programs for Credit Union technical training needs by keeping a working knowledge
 of Credit Unions operations, products, services, systems, technologies and related training materials.
- Maintained currency in training/eLearning, instructional methodologies and technologies and educational/regulatory courses.
- Participated in project management teams to ensure training programs for new systems and technologies are developed and implemented in a timely manner – including implementing and developing training materials and courses for Microsoft CRM.
- Establish project objectives and plans by co-coordinating and collaborating with other departments, vendors, subject matter experts, senior managers and executives.

STRAVINSOFT July 2003 to May 2004

Director of Sales and Marketing

- Designed and implemented Sales and Marketing programs for software start-up StravinSOFT Inc.
- Developed all internal inter-departmental processes and documentation, and developed overall company and product branding, including company website, collateral, as well as coaching and motivating sales staff.
- Position involved establishing sales commission structures and territories, as well as developing Alliance Partner programs with FileMaker, Independent Developers and other SQL companies.
- Evaluated initial product and customer needs, and recommended three additional product versions to add additional marketplaces for company.
- Participated in Investor meetings on behalf of technical and sales staff to further grow our overall start-up funding.

CANDLE CORPORATION

June 1998 to July 2003

Senior Field Marketing Manager

- Developed yearly marketing plan for company's multiple software products to increase sales in 11 state region
- Worked with Region Executives to develop appropriate marketing and customer events to generate pipeline and increase revenue in Global Fortune 500 accounts.
- Used Tradeshows, User Groups and other strategic events to drive customer awareness and product branding.
- Worked with multiple Product Business Units to develop current customer and prospect marketing programs.
- Aided the Western Region, as well as Global and Regional account managers in making their yearly quota's for three consecutive years.
- Analyzed marketplace and developed strategic campaigns to increase market share of two software product lines
 By developing and implementing Internet marketing tactics; including website development.

Skills

- Adobe Flash certified, Mobile application & Website conversion, additional Adobe Design product skills; multiple CRM/DB tools-Seibel, Sales Force, Microsoft CRM, Zoho; Website design products-Word press, Flash, Premiere, HTML, multiple web cast technologies; various Social Networking tools such as Google Analytics, various Marketing Automation solutions, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, Google +, Hoot Suite, Tweet Deck
- Database Software (Access etc.), Graphics Software (Photoshop etc.), Personal computers, Microsoft Office suite (and similar software), Web design software, Peripheral devices (including network connectivity maintenance), Hardware device maintenance

Education

- El Centro College Dallas, TX Current (AAS Internet Development Technologies Interactive Media
 & Marketing Specialization/Certifications)-Student & STEM program intern; President, IT Society club
- Canada College Redwood City, CA 1987 Early Childhood Education (E.C.E) degree